Hello welcome back friends in today's video
we will see how to
insure a two wheeler bike from Il Lamba Bank through CSC
so let's
start the video and what is the complete
process, let's see in detail,
here we have to complete the login from the Digital Save portal,
after that
as our dashboard opens here,
now to insure a two wheeler bike through CSC,
click on the insurance option here, here on the top side
one can see the insurance here,
now here the motor third
party option has to be selected here, as
soon as we click here,
after that many services of motor third
party are given here, in today's video
we are going to insure a two wheeler of Il Lamba Bank here,
so here we have to
click on the motor third party Il Lamba Bank general insurance option,
so here the dashboard of Il Lamba Bank general
insurance opens here, so
many services are given here,
now we have to do third party insurance of two wheeler bike here  To
do this,
click on the two-wheeler two-wheeler option here. If you
click here, then a
dashboard like this will be visible in front of us.
After entering the registration number of the bike here,
click on the Get RTO details option here. If you do this, then
all the information of the bike gets
filled automatically here, like the
model number of the bike and everything is here, the
manufacture date, everything is visible here.
After the details are verified, click on the Get Quote option
here. Then you will
see the total premium here. After that,
click on the proceed option here. If you
click on the proceed option here, then the
proposal details are visible here. The
total premium is 843. Along with this,
all the information of the vehicle details can be
seen here, where the
state from which this bike would have been purchased is shown here,
after that other details are shown
here.  The engine number and chassis number
of the bike can be seen and along with this,
click on the option of add nominee details
here. If you want to add a nominee here, then to
add a nominee, you have to
fill the name of the nominee here. Also, the
relationship has to be selected here.
After that, fill the age of the nominee
here. If you want to
complete the KYC here, then to complete the KYC,
click on the KYC option here. Now,
here you
get to see three types of options for doing KYC,
PAN card, Aadhar card and
driving license here. So, if
you have any one of these three documents, then
you have to complete your KYC here
because doing KYC is mandatory here.
If you do not do KYC, then
you will not be able to make a claim here through any accident. So,
Aadhar
card is present with everyone here.  If yes, then you have to
complete the KYC from Aadhar card here. Now here
first of all you have to enter the Aadhar number,
after that enter the full name here
as it is recorded in your Aadhar card. The
date of birth as recorded in Aadhar card has to be
filled from here.
After filling, select the gender here, whether male
or female, then
select it here. After that, let
it remain ticked on no here. Also, after
clicking on the ticked option,
click on the submit option here. And
as you click on the submit option,
you have to wait a little here.
Now if the KYC verification field
shows in front of you here, then
click on the upload now option here and
upload your file here manually. After that,
for proof of identity, you have to upload any one file like Aadhar
card, driving license or voter ID
here
manually, the file size here can be
JPG, JPEG and PDF file
here.  It should be here inside AB.
To upload, click on the choose file option.
You have to
upload it here from the folder in which you have kept your file. After both the files are uploaded,
now click on the all option here.
Here the document has been submitted
successfully and it has been
uploaded. As you can see,
KYC and submit manual process, so
click on the ok option here.
Now our KYC has been done here, it is done
automatically here. Your
name here and all the details here are
automatically filled here through KYC.
Now friends, you have to enter your email ID,
mobile number and PAN card here.
After entering, now
click on the generate proposal option here.
After that, here friends,
you get to see the proposal number here.
Here you get to see the total premium,
so click on the check box here and click on the
A option here.
After that, friends, click on the CSC here.
Here it will redirect you to the payment page gate.
Now you have to
enter the CSC password here.
After entering the PIN,
click on the pay option here. As soon as you
click on the pay option,
your payment gets completed successfully here.
After this,
congratulations, you have successfully generated a
policy. Find the bill details here. Now
friends, after the policy is completed here,
you get to see the policy number here.
Along with this, you can see the start date
and end date of the policy here.
Friends, here you get to see
an option to download the policy
here. So
click on this tab here.
Friends, here the policy has been successfully
downloaded here.
So, you get to see this PDF file like this.
After that, you have to print this PDF
file here. After printing, you have to
provide it to the customer here.
Now friends, after the insurance is completed,
how much will you have to pay here?
To see the commission you have received,
you have to come to the digital portal and
click on the order history option here and then
click on the details option here, like
details here, after that friends,
you have received a commission of ₹1 here,
friends, here you get a good
commission of about ₹1 here, here you
get to see through CSC,
ICICI Lamba General Third Party for bike
insurance, so friends,
that's all you get in today's video, friends, till then
in the next video,
please like, share and subscribe to the video,
thank you for watching the video, Jai Hind
[Music]